# Raghavendra M P () Featured

Software Engineer seeking assignments in Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Hibernate, Spring Mvc, Core Java, Struts, J2Ee, JSP, Spring Boot, Angular 2



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Slk Software Services Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree:

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Hibernate, Spring Mvc, Core

Java, Struts, J2Ee, JSP, Spring Boot, Angular 2

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

## **Summary**

Proficiency in grasping new technical concepts quickly and utilizing the same in a productive manner.

A proactive learner with a flair for adopting emerging trends & addressing industry requirements to achieve organizational objectives & profitability norms.

Has the motivation to take independent responsibility as well as ability to contribute and be a productive team player. Good team member, positive attitude, result oriented, Self-motivated, quick learner, willing to adapt to new challenges & new technologies.

Total experience: 4 years

## **Work Experience**

**SIk Software Services** as Software Engineer Jul 2018 to Till Date

**Invenger Tecnologies** as System Analyst Sep 2017 to Jun 2018

Think n Solutions Software Technologies as Java Developer Jan 2017 to Sep 2017

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Visveswaraiah Technological University (VTU) in 2015

PG: in 0

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
CORE JAVA, J2EE		2017	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Servlet, WebServices	1.7	2017	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
HTML, Jsp, JQuery, Angular JS,Angular 2			
JavaScript and css			
MS-SQL, MySQL,DB2 and Oracle			
Apache tomcat , Jenkins, Wild fly			
IBM WEBSPHERE			
Tortoise SVN and GIT			
Eclipse, Edit plus, SQLyog , IBM RAD			
JASPER			
WINDOWS			
Hibernate, Struts 2.0, Spring MVC			
springboot			

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
kannada	Expert			
hindi	Proficient			
telugu	Proficient			

## **Projects**

Project Title: booking ticket portal

Client: unknown

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Aug 2015 - May 2016
Project Location: Bengaluru Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Role: Programmer Team Size: 15

Skill Used: Java, J2EE, Struts 2, Hibernate 3.0 MySQL 5.5, Tomcat 7, Eclipse LunaLog4J, CSS 3, JavaScript. Role Description: Involved in Coding. Developing the web application using struts framework. Use Hibernate framework for the java objects persistence in database. Developing the User interfaces using JSP, Html. Project Details: Booking Ticket Portal is used to book movie tickets from online like BookMyShow.com and Ticketmaster.com. User can also book tickets for Plays Sports and Events. This web application gives you a personalized touch where you can login using Facebook, Google+ and get recommended events based on your booking history. You can get details about the movies based on your location selected. This web application is basically being developed for only three cities i.e. Bangalore, Chennai and Hyderabad. About 60 percent of its transactions take place via its mobile app which, say experts, is the most successful mobile ecommerce app in the country. Apart from being an online ticketing portal, Booking Ticket Portal provides offers information about upcoming movies and events, show timings, venue details, artist bios and trailers. Booking Ticket Portal occupies 85 to 90 percent of the online entertainment-ticketing market.

## **Affirmative Action**

#### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

**Employment Status: Full time**